{
    "subject": "Terry_Farrell__actress_",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Brian_Baker__actor_",
    "human_readable": "Terry Farrell, the actress, is married to Brian Baker, the actor.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9800758957862854,
            "question": "Name the actor who is married to Terry Farrell."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9653229117393494,
            "question": "Who is the actor married to Terry Farrell?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.92661452293396,
            "question": "Is Terry Farrell's spouse an actor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9254734516143799,
            "question": "Are both Terry Farrell and Brian Baker actors?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9182687401771545,
            "question": "Who is Terry Farrell married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9128838181495667,
            "question": "Is Terry Farrell an actress?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8919360041618347,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Terry Farrell and Brian Baker?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7116450071334839,
            "question": "What is the profession of Terry Farrell's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41881072521209717,
            "question": "What profession does Brian Baker have?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2516484260559082,
            "question": "What does Brian Baker do for a living?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Terry Farrell, the actress, is married to Brian Baker, the actor.",
            "html": "yago_4230_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What profession does Brian Baker have?",
            "html": "yago_4230_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the profession of Terry Farrell's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_4230_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the relationship between Terry Farrell and Brian Baker?",
            "html": "yago_4230_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4230_115.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4230_123.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4230_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4230_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4230_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4230_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4230_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4230_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4230_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4230_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples you'd like me to evaluate!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that Terry Farrell was married to Brian Baker, who is an actor. This aligns with the query stating that Terry Farrell (the actress) is married to Brian Baker (the actor)."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": true,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}